Guide to the Office of Administration and Facilities, Eileen Buckley 1959-1995 (Bulk 1964-1989) RG 8.0 RG 8.0
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files
  - Washington Square Southeast - Message Sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Message Sheets, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Minutes of Planning Commission Conference, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Plans and Drawings-Floorplans, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Plans and Drawings-Studies, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Project Development Plan I, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Project Development Plan II, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Publicity, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Redevelopment Plan, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Redevelopment Plan, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Street Closings, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Tenants, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Third Revision of Urban Renewal Plan, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Washington Square Village, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square Southeast - Washington Square Village, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Village - Management Conversion, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058471 9
  - Washington Square Village - Refinancing, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Village - Study, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square West - 29, 1966-1984 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square West - 29, 1971-1985 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square West - 37, 1962-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square West - 37, 1966-1980 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Washington Square West - 37, 1974-1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square West - 37, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Watson, Glegg, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Waverly Place - 10, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Waverly Place - 12-18, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Waverly Place - 14, 1965-1969 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Waverly Place - 18, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Weehawken, NJ, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Weinberg, Sydney, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Weissman, Gerald, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - West, Richard, undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Whealey, Richard, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - White, Carol, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Wilkes, John, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Williams, Lawrence, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Williams, Luther, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Pat, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Williamson, Sam, undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Winder, Richard, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Wismar, Keith, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Women of Color, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Women's Forum Education Award, undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Wreen, Peggy, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Wright, Paul, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - WSV - Commercial Areas, 1960-1971 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - WSV - Commercial Areas, 1964-1983 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - WSV - Commercial Areas, 1970-1985 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - WSV - Floorplans and Photos, undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - WSV - Tenant Correspondence, undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - WSV - Tenant Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - WSV - Tenant Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - WSV - Updated Appraisal, undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - X, Malcolm, undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Xerox, undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Yadrick, John, undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Yale University - Dept. of French, undated (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Yivo, undated (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Zoning, undated (Box 44, Folder 45)